# ARIELE BONIFÁCIO

## **DETAILS**

#### **PHONE**

+49 172 6425581

#### **EMAIL**

arielebonifacio@gmail.com

## LINKS

Linkedin

**GitHub** 

Acclaim Open Badges

## **SKILLS**

Communication

Agile Scrum

Git

**Customer Support** 

SOL

HTML5

CSS3

Design Thinking

User Interface/ User Experience

JavaScript

# **LANGUAGES**

English

## **PROFILE**

Hallo, I'm Ariele, a passionate student of front-end development, agile methodology, and - why not - the German language.

I'm graduated in System Development and now I'm studying the UX Design discipline. I'm also certified as Professional Scrum Master.

Worked in areas such as technical support, end-user assistance, learning management systems (LMS), and deployment, I'm fully experienced in customer service.

My goals are to become a front-end developer and working with agile teams and help to create long-lasting business relationships.

## **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

## Deployment Analyst, ISAT

Aug 2020 — May 2022

Control tasks and deadlines for customization requested and keep constant contact with customers. Understand all your needs and carry out the planning of the implantation process, as well the training and the initial configurations regarding the acquired LMS (Learning Management System) platform, provide any type of support during the implantation process.

#### Support Analyst, Proxxi

Jul 2018 — Sep 2020

Remote end-user first-level support acting on incidents and requests records. Management of incoming work queue and engagement of customer and local support teams.

#### System Analyst, ISAT

Feb 2017 — Jul 2018

Deployment of Learning Management System (LMS) systems for new customers including the initial configuration and data move/lift. Act as client-facing support assisting with tools, reports, and prioritizing new functionalities and requests backlog.

Portuguese

## **EDUCATION**

### Analysis and Systems Development, FATEC

Jul 2015 — Aug 2019

### User Experience, Anhembi Morumbi

Apr 2020 — Jul 2021

## **CERTIFICATION**

## Professional Scrum Master™ I (PSM I), Scrum.org

Jan 2020

## **INTERNSHIPS**

## Support Analyst, ISAT

Brazil

Nov 2015 — Feb 2017

Support related to e-mail accounts and domains, managing user tickets and controlling streaming and chat.

## **EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

**Bootcamp UX Design, How Bootcamps** 

Jun 2020 — Aug 2020